Gianpiero Condorelli

Software Engineer

Address: Flat 212, 122 High Street, M4 1AB, Manchester, United Kingdom

Phone: +44 (0) 7900 541804

E-mail: gia.condorelli@gmail.com

Website: https://www.gianpierocondorelli.com

Profile

Software Engineer with 3+ years experience equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Proficient in various platforms and languages. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

Skills

- Languages: C, Java, Scala, Rust, HTML, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python.
- Frameworks: Angular2+, Spring, Node.JS
- Platforms: Oracle DB, MySQL, Apache HTTP Server, MongoDB, Apache Impala, Apache Sqoop, Apache Hadoop.
- Operative Systems: Microsoft Windows, Linux, Mac OS X, Android, iOS
- Editors and Office Tools: Microsoft Office Suite, GSuite, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Oracle SQL Developer

Experience

Booking.com Transport Ltd, Manchester, United Kingdom.

Software Engineer 2019-today

Work productively with the Product Managers to understand requirements and business needs around Data Tooling. Developed solutions using Node.JS, Scala, Rust and Java coupling the solution with the company standards at the time (e.g. Observability, Resilence). Continuous learning thanks to code review session and learning time.

TamTamy Reply, Milan, Italy

IT Consultant 2017-2019

I had mainly the role of Full Stack Developer building Web Apps with Angular framework - for the Front End - and the Spring framework - for the Back End, following the entire lifecycle of the software engineering - from requirements gathering with customers to the final delivery. Recently, thanks to a project I'm involved, I entered in the world of the Data Engineering.

Accenture, Milan, Italy

Analyst 2017-2019

In the experience in this company I had the role of Junior PMO.

Education

Università degli Studi di Catania, Catania, Italy

Master's degree in Computer Engineering 2015-2017

Graduation Grade 109/110

Thesis Title: Enabling Smart Object Secure Communication in Publish/Subscribe Architectures
Università degli Studi di Catania, Catania, Italy

Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering **2011-2015**

Graduation Grade: 99/110

The final project was the building of a mobile app for Windows Phone for the tracking of physical activities.

Languages

- 1. Italian Native
- 2. English Working knowledge

Gianpiero Condorelli — gia.condorelli@gmail.com — +44 (0) 7900 541804